Hi, we're here to help you find great new colors for your skin tone.
So you've come to the right place.
My name is Sylvia Russell.
As you can see, our model has fair skin, very beautiful skin.
So we're not going to use colors that are over powering on the skin.
Now when you have a light skin, or cool tones, think cool and when you think cool, I think blue, green, colors that will help to compliment your skin tone.
It's important to know what your skin tone is so that you can choose the right color.
Now again, if you have cool skin or light skin, then you can apply colors that are blue, green, nothing very very orange or warm.
If you have medium skin you may want to go with your taupes, your peaches, your creamy oranges, nothing too too orange.
And if you have dark skin, then you'll want to go ahead and enhance the color with a brighter more vibrant shade.
Remember if you can find a pallet like mine here that gives you an option of several different colors.
You have some warms, you have some cools, you have some darks.
Test these products out on your skin and find the right colors to help you achieve the look that you want.
My name is Sylvia Russell and this is how you can choose colors for your skin tone.